He's Tee.
My school friend.
He'll sleep here tonight.
Don't tell me that...
you're BKBOii.
That's too close.
Why?
Can't I be close to you?
How can a gay kiss a man
and not get punched in real life?
Like it?
Just beacuse I didn't punch means I like it?
Shall we try?
If a friend kiss you,
won't you punch him?
You can punch me.
Who could ever punch you?
What if that friend likes you?
Will you punch him?
Do I have to punch you?
About the kiss?
Um.
You can punch me,
but don't hit too hard.
Are you really gonna do it?
I probably forgot to punch you.
I think I felt very down on that day.
Don't you think?
Um.
What about today?
Today?
Can we try again?
I want to know that I...
Are you angry?
I think I'm slow to anger.
Can you feel it?
Nope.
Feels like kissing a log.
Really?
Yeah.
Um.
If you say so.
Then go to sleep.
You can punch me
because I feel really good.
I'll never forget this night.
Good night.
Think you're handsome?
It's on.
You're done.
Shit!
Tee, it's late.
Tee.
It's late.
It's late now.
Give me a few more minutes.
I give you five sec.
Can I have ten sec?
Fine.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Tee, it's already ten sec.
Um.
Hurry up.
Boo!
What are you doing? You startled me.
Good morning, Pa.
Fine, morning. Nihao.
Hello, Pa.
This side too.
Lovely.
That's my dad.
But this is mine.
Dad is still here.
Where are you rushing off to?
Do you have anything for a quick bite?
For a quick bite...
Uh.
Um.
What did you cook?
Sandwiches.
What did you put in it?
Chilli sauce.
It's spicy.
Tee, let's go.
-We're leaving now, Dad.
-Goodbye.
You should get some water.
A new regulation of our school.
Whoever applies tone-up cream,
don't let me find out.
(Teacher Banjong.)
Slay.
Oh.
(BKBOii blocked you.)
Frame, you're late. Come here.
Oh. Hi, Som.
Chill out.
I've got something for you.
It's a rare one. Not easy to find.
-Go, line up.
-See ya.
Oh, Frame.
Hello, Teacher.
How have you been?
Let's do a TikTok dance together later.
Okay.
Rehearse, rehearse.
See you at noon.
Goodbye.
Hey, don't be late next time.
The rest of you, follow me.
Do it strongly.
Like I do.
-I also do it strongly.
-Tee, come on.
Suraphong, you aren't pulling your weight.
Tee.
Hurry up.
Come on, move.
Fuse, do you still feel spicy?
Of course.
Do you want to try?
Try?
Like last night?
Tee.
We should go now.
Wait a sec.
Let me tuck my shirt in first. Just a sec.
Come on.
Isn't it good that we can do morning assembly together?
Teeratat.
Yes.
Thanyawat.
You're late again.
I apologize. I woke up late.
No, I'm late.
I woke up the latest.
Why are you holding his hand?
Go, line up.
Um.
Line up.
Teacher Banjong.
We came together.
So what?
Line up.
Um.
Rules are rules.
Regulations are regulations.
Thirty squat jumps.
Teacher Banjong.
Can I take the punishment for my friend?
Um.
You're both late, so you have to get punished together.
You can't do it for your friend. Do it. Pay attention.
(Rodtang.)
Hello, pretty teacher.
Line up, line up.
Are you Fuse?
I'm Rodtang from Grade 10.
I'm a fan of yours.
I liked and shared your video.
Really?
My video?
Your school introduction video.
Wow.
I also bought Fing's facial mask.
I used it and my face feels so soft.
If you don't believe me, you can touch it.
Um, it's actually soft.
(Tee 0 - 1 Rodtang)
What's wrong with your lips?
Is it that obvious?
Looks like you're posing a duck face.
A duck face?
Like this.
Looks like you want a kiss.
Can you feel it?
Nope.
You can punch me
because I feel really good.
Don't think I won't dare to punch you.
I'm kidding. Are you actually going to punch me?
Hey.
I didn't mean that.
Not to tell you what to do, but you shouldn't make threats like that.
Ah.
They'll think you're blushing.
Blushing, my ass.
For real.
Go, let's go.
Where to?
Come with me.
(Tee 1 - 1 Rodtang)
Take me with you.
Wait for me, Suraphong.
Suraphong.
Fuse.
Oh, Fuse.
I saw it.
Saw what?
Enough, guys.
How did you see that?
I thought you were shooting a series.
Very outstanding.
What series?
Wit!
What did I do wrong?
I'm more curious as to...
why did you two come together today?
You mean Rodtang?
Well...
Tee slept at my home last night.
Huh?
When did you get close to him?
When you slept at his home?
No wonder...
Tee wasn't in a late-for-school line.
You brought the misbehavior disease to him.
I guess...
this disease spreads through saliva.
What the hell are you saying?
We didn't kiss.
What?
I mean...
you two drooled over each other.
Oh.
You've got to tell us.
Tee and you.
How close are you two now?
What we don't know,
tells us everything.
Tell us now.
Go ahead.
Tell us.
Ugh.
Are you going to pick up?
Right, I just saw Jeen with the same man.
Where did you see them?
At BTS.
Oh no.
Are you okay?
You can tell us everything.
-Does something bother you?
-Seeing you act like this makes us worry.
Come on. Sit down.
Come on.
Forget about it.
Let's play UNO.
Oh.
Let's continue the game.
Whose turn is it?
What are you doing?
Do you want others to know that...
we are in the same bathroom?
What do you want?
You can't do this.
Didn't you get a tattoo for other people to look at?
The reason I got it...
is none of your business.
Fine.
I won't look at it.
But I'll wait and see it in your account.
Can you unblock me?
No.
What is the password?
After this,
don't block me.
Don't unfollow me.
I donate to you every month.
But...
donators are not gods.
You're handsome.
But I'm not sure...
if you've got the moves.
Wanna do it now?
Don't you want to try it?
Let me go.
Frame. I'm scared.
I'm sorry.
Then don't talk big next time.
How cute.
(You disappeared.)
Should I call her back?
Fuse.
Oh!
Nai.
You startled me.
You startle, but I'm stressed.
Please come to practice.
The big day is almost here.
I'm just a second drum major.
No need to practice too much.
Are you a school drum major?
I'm just a second drum major.
He has been a drum major from Grade 1 to Grade 6.
He can be the first drum major,
but he is too lazy.
Damn, that's cool.
So you can do double-baton twirling?
Easy peasy. I can even do triple-baton twirling.
You can do triple-baton twirling.
But...
I have three legs.
Ooh.
I've seen it.
It's like this.
Where is a three-legged person?
I want to take a look.
Wit!
What?
Why?
You have to practice tomorrow.
At evening.
Don't flake on me again.
Nai.
I didn't say I'm free.
Is your third leg this small?
A person who said mine is small,
they begging for their life like this.
Frame, please.
Don't you believe me?
Nai.
I'm not sure whether I'm free tomorrow.
I'll let you know.
What will you do tomorrow?
Tee!
Tee, why aren't you with your friends?
Need some time apart. It’s getting bored.
Wait.
Are you bored with Fuse?
No, I can see him every day.
Or are you gonna hit on Fuse?
Can I?
What's going on?
What are you talking about?
Gotcha.
What did we miss?
Hello.
Are you free?
Could you help me carry stuff?
Eh?
We're having lunch.
Fuse.
Hmm?
I'll go to your house today.
Huh?
Why would you come to my house again?
Look.
(Come over this evening. I want you to do the product review.)
When did you talk to my sis?
She ask me to help her.
Or are you flirting with my sis?
Why should I flirt with her?
I would rather flirt with you.
Fuse.
Did you guys really plan to meet each other?
No one is here.
Masks are on the table.
Read the instructions and do it yourself.
Please take nice photos of them.
So you have to do it?
And also take pics by yourself?
Good luck, bro.
I'm out.
Fuse.
Could you help me, please?
Can I have some?
Okay.
Don't move yet.
Can we stay like this for a minute?
I'm so happy.
What about you?
Are you happy too?
I'm back.
Hey.
Don't slack off.
I know.
Chill out.
Hello, Jie Fing.
Hi.
Hello, Yaimai.
Not leaving?
Well, I'm leaving.
Do whatever you want.
Make yourself at home.
I love it.
Who told you to call my sis Jie?
Well, can I call you Nong Fuse?
Shall Nong Fuse get back to reviewing the product?
Stop it.
I'll go to the restroom. Gonna throw up.
Hurry back, Nong Fuse.
Are you confused?
Yeah.
Stupid.
That's my name.
I'm so happy.
What about you?
Are you happy too?
Gosh.
Are you having dirty thoughts?
No way.
Alright.
Is our class rep absent today?
Yes, he's absent.
Then we're gonna select a temporary class rep today.
Any volunteers?
Oh, Thanyawat.
Do you volunteer to be a class rep?
Give him applause.
Great job.
Today, we're going to learn about love.
Raise your hand if you're in love.
Anyone?
Oh, Thanyawat.
Aw.
You're in love with whom? Tell me.
I love friends.
Consider it passed.
Anyone else?
Okay, let's say today had its good moments.
And no homework for today.
(Sorry, the number you have dialed...)
Hello.
Bring these files to Teacher Anthony to sign them.
And bring them back to Teacher's room, okay?
Here you go.
Yes.
Well, where is he?
That's a class rep's responsibility.
Find him and get his signature.
Okay?
If you can't do it alone, ask your friends for help.
Where is Frame?
He's already gone.
Well, can you guys help me?
How can we help you?
Hey, we can't.
We're playing ranked right now.
Nobody leaves the game.
Yeah.
Nadech.
How can I help you?
Have you seen Teacher Anthony?
Ah.
I haven't seen him.
Hey.
Where are you going?
Whoa, you nailed it.
Fuse!
Are you skipping a class?
You kidding? It's you who skipped a class.
I didn't.
I'm practicing for the show at Siam this evening.
Will you come to see me perform?
I'm busy.
Well, it's okay.
I'll show you first before anyone else.
I'm also busy now.
It feels cool in this spot.
Whoa.
Have you played it since you were born?
Nah.
I've played it since my past life.
Hm.
And... can you play it?
I can't.
Here, I'll show you how.
First, place your hand like this.
How?
Hey.
Ouch.
Uh...
I gotta go.
See you.
Hey, Fuse.
Hey.
Where are you going?
Why are you rushing?
Nothing.
Right, Mo told me that you've gone home.
I'm about to leave.
I have to go now.
Frame.
What?
Since you're the most experienced in our group,
Experience?
Do you think...
someone can kiss a person that they aren't into?
It's just lips touching, isn't it?
No need to think that much.
Really?
If you don't believe it, you can try.
Hey.
Can I try?
Close your eyes.
Ouch!
Gosh.
I can't do it.
You take forever to realize how you feel.
I thought I had to kiss you for real.
You said it's possible.
It's possible for someone,
but not for me.
And neither do you, right?
I guess...
people like us,
if we let someone kiss us,
that person must be very special to us.
Or maybe we like them a lot.
Do you think the same as I do?
Why did you ask about this?
Did you let someone kiss you?
Hey!
I didn't kiss.
I didn't like it.
I did nothing.
What's going on with him?
Fuse.
If you ever want to try it again,
you can try it with me.
(If a friend kisses you,)
(won't you punch him?)
(That's too close.)
(Why? Can't I be close to you?)
(I guess people like us,)
(if we let someone kiss us,)
(that person must be very special to us.)
(You can punch me)
(because I feel really good.)
Are you hurt?
(I guess people like us,)
(if we let someone kiss us,)
(that person must be very special to us.)
Fuse.
Uh.
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at the cake.
It looks delicious.
This is the teacher's.
If you want to have it,
I'll buy it for you.
Hey, I'm kidding.
Well, I gotta go.
Walk carefully.
Don't run.
Um.
Have a good day.
What do you want?
I want the truth.
About Tee and you.
Are you close to him?
Nah.
Nah? He was looking at you.
Are you trying to skip a class?
I'm trying to be with you.
Jeen.
Fuse.
I have no idea.
About...
what I am to you right now.
Jeen.
I think we'd better break up.